那么我们建造了一架足够强大的机器
So we built a machine powerful enough
通过大爆炸创造出一个新的神速力
to big-bang a new Speed Force into existence
而这完全依靠
based solely on the teachings
史上最邪恶的极速者的指导
of history's most evil Speedster.
我们确定要按下开关吗
Are we sure we wanna hit this switch?
动手吧
Do it.
人造神速力
点火
什么情况
Uh, what's happening?
没有成功
It didn't work.
闪 电 侠
第六季
第十七集
大家在里面吗
Guys, you in there?
抱歉打断
Sorry to interrupt--oh.
机器测试进展如何
How'd the machine test go?
根本无法启动
Well, it didn't.
问题就在于此
That's the problem.
斯旺怎么能完全靠他自己的能力
How did Thawne manage to build
建造一架神速力机器
a Speed Force machine on his own
还不依靠笔记的帮助
without a journal to guide him,
而尖端科研实验室所有的脑力合在一起
but all the brainpower in S.T.A.R. Labs
都无法让这东西启动
can't even get this thing to work.
我们不过建了个十二吨重的镇纸
It's like we built a 12-ton paper weight.
好吧  好吧  不过
Okay, okay, but hey!
也许出去散散心
Maybe getting out of here for a minute
能帮你们理清思绪
might clear your heads.
我自己  正打算去一趟
I, myself, was on my way over
《公民报》那
to "The Citizen' right now.
有没有人想  巴里  想不想我和我一起去
Does anybody--Barry-- wanna come with me?
不了  听着
No. Look.
这台机器无法运转的每一天
Every day that the machine is off
我都无法保护这座城市
is another day I can't protect this city.
我得继续研究
I have to keep working.
巴里  等等
Barry, wait.
你确定你不想见爱瑞丝吗
Are you sure you don't wanna see Iris?
需要我帮你带话给她吗
Can I tell her anything for you?
告诉她  我想她
Tell her I miss her.
他的速度每时每刻都在流失
His speed has been draining non-stop.
你的计划很成功
Your plan was a success.
你们干得很漂亮
You've done an amazing job.
一切都还好吗
Is everything okay?
你看上去  心不在焉
You seem...distant.
抱歉
Sorry, um...
我只不过想知道你是否需要我们
I'd just like to know if you want us to proceed
进行下一阶段
with the next phase.
是的
Yes.
去和你们的兄弟碰头  做好准备
Go join your brother and prepare.
因为今晚
Because tonight...
我终于能够解放了
I will finally have my liberation.
保证成功
Success is assured.
进来
Come in.
你们好  在忙吗
Hey. You busy?
你好  有什么事
Hey. What's up?
我想
I just wanted to...
你是为我和巴里的事情而来的吗
You're here about me and Barry?
是的
Yeah.
爱瑞丝  他状况很糟糕
He's in a really bad place, Iris.
他的心很受伤
His heart is breaking.
而他不愿意和任何人交流
He won't talk to anybody about it.
在他把诺拉带回未来之后  他承诺过我
He promised me after he took Nora to the future
那将是他最后一次在没有我的情况下
that would be the last time that he made a decision
对我们家的事做出决定
about our family without me.
然后他让我爸参加联邦证人保护计划
But then he took my dad into Witsec
都没告诉我
and didn't even tell me.
还是辛格告诉我的
I had to find out from Singh.
你是怎么克服的  塞西尔
How do you get over that, Cecile?
就...
Well, it--
我真的不知道  爱瑞丝
I don't really know, Iris.
但我想第一步是想要
But I would think the first step is wanting to.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我不知道
I-- I don't know.
你能感觉到我想要什么吗
Can you feel what I want?
你能告诉我吗
Can you tell me?
你感觉
You feel...
难过
sad.
难过又担心
Sad and concerned.
我想爱瑞丝现在需要的是空间
I think what Iris needs right now is space
去专心思考真正重要的是什么
to focus on what's really important.
没错
Right.
现在重要的是我要照顾好自己  塞西尔
It's important for me to take care of myself right now, Cecile.
好吧
Okay, yeah.
你丈夫希望我告诉你  他想你
Your husband wanted me to tell you that he misses you.
巴仔
Bar?
你把门堵住了
There's something blocking the door.
是
Yeah...
你不是还在极速实验室吗
I thought you were still at the Speed Lab.
-巴里  -等等
- Hey, Barry. - Hold on.
我为什么不能进自己家
Why can't I get inside my own house?
抱歉  等等
Sorry. Hold on.
-等一下  -天呐
- One second. - Geez!
塞西尔  我可以解释
Cecile, I can explain.
你这是在搞什么
What the hell is this?
爱瑞丝不是爱瑞丝
Iris isn't Iris.
然后我想很明显
So then I thought well obviously,
这不可能是爱瑞丝来自另一个地球的二重身
this can't be an Iris doppelganger from another Earth
因为二重身已经不复存在了
because doppelgangers don't exist anymore.
因为多元宇宙已经不复存在了
Because the Multiverse doesn't exist anymore.
因为危机把多元宇宙都毁了  对吧
Because Crisis blew it all up, right?
没错
Exactly.
所以如果这是真的
So if that's true,
我们知道还有谁会假扮爱瑞丝吗
who else do we know that could be pretending to be Iris?
-我...  什么  -变形人
- I-- what-- - Shapeshifters.
任意人是我第一个怀疑对象
All right, so Everyman was my first suspect.
西斯科的报告显示在危机之后  他还活着
And Cisco's report show that he is alive post-Crisis.
然后我想到穿越者说起过塑胶机器人
Then I remembered something that Breacher said about Plastoids.
这让我想到
Which made me realize,
这个地球现在也许有变形火星人
there could be shapeshifting Martians on this Earth now.
这个假爱瑞丝
This-- this fake Iris
甚至都不一定是我们这个星球上的
doesn't even have to be from our planet.
然后我想到  如果我们身边隐藏着火星人
But then, it hit me that J'onn J'onzz would sense
荣恩·荣兹会察觉到
if there was a Martian hidden among us,
所以这个想法说不通
so that was a dead end,
但是这让我有了最大的突破
but it led me to my biggest breakthrough yet.
塞西尔  这一切开始的那晚
Okay, Cecile, the night that this all started,
爱瑞丝离家去调查一条新闻
Iris left to investigate a story.
我分析过她的手机定位
I analyzed her phone's GPS
上面显示她去了麦克洛奇技术公司
and it shows that she went to McCulloch Tech.
塞西尔  我觉得爱瑞丝那晚发生了一些事
Cecile, I think that something happened to Iris that night.
巴里  所有这些
Barry... All of this-- is this
就是你一直躲着爱瑞丝的原因
the reason you've been avoiding Iris?
那不是爱瑞丝
That's not Iris!
好吧  听着  我不想
Okay, look--I didn't want to
在找到更多证据之前告诉别人这事
tell anyone else about this until I gathered more evidence,
但现在你知道了  所以我...
but now you know, so I--
你怎么想
what do you think?
我怎么想  我怎么想
What do I think? What do I think?
我觉得  我觉得这个听起来
I think--I think that this-this sounds--
我知道听起来什么样  但是你看
I know how it sounds, but look.
我们见过更疯狂的
We've seen crazier.
我们见过更疯狂的  看看这些线索
We've seen crazier. And look at all the clues.
我是说  她突然开始说起意大利语
Okay, I mean, she speaks Italian all of a sudden.
她用瓶子砸了一个家伙的头
She smashed a bottle over some guy's head.
她做的煎饼出奇地好吃
She made incredible pancakes.
塞西尔  相信我  爱瑞丝可不会做煎饼
Cecile, trust me. Iris can't make pancakes.
懂了吗  但是最大的线索是
All right? But the biggest clue was...
她把我赶走了
Her throwing me out.
真正的爱瑞丝绝不会停止为我们俩斗争
The real Iris would never stop fighting for us.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, um.
亲爱的
Sweetie.
你觉不觉得或许  只是或许
Do you think that maybe-just maybe--
你感觉到了一丝恐惧
you're feeling a little scared, you know.
因为你的婚姻遇上
Because your marriage is going through
一些阻挠  因此或许
a rough patch, and maybe,
你需要的仅仅是去见见爱瑞丝
what you need to do is just go see Iris.
那不是爱瑞...  塞西尔  你看
That's not Ir-Cecile, look.
你知道为什么我的神速力计量表一直红着
Do you know why my Speed Gauge is still glowing red?
因为就在我
It is because the moment
踏出公寓的那一刻  我意识到
that I stepped out of the loft, I realized
爱瑞丝  真正的爱瑞丝  我妻子
Iris, the real Iris, my wife,
她在其他地方
she is somewhere else.
很可能处于危险之中
Probably in danger.
如果这是真的  我需要我取回我的神速
And if that's true, I need my speed back.
我的闪电  我所有的能力来拯救她
My--my lightning, all my powers if I'm gonna save her.
这是我在那之后唯一想过的事情
It's all I've thought about ever since.
不管这一切听起来有多疯狂
No matter how insane this all sounds,
我心里很清楚
I know in my heart
真正的爱瑞丝
that the real Iris
是在别的地方
is out there somewhere.
等着我去找到她
Waiting for me to find her.
我不会让她失望的
I won't let her down.
北极熊有点太没创意了吧
Polar bear's a little on the nose, don't you think?
商店里又没有
Well, it's not like the stores have a
"双重刺客袭击后  愿你尽快恢复"卡
"Get well soon from dual light-assassin attacks" Card.
你带了什么
What'd you bring?
我带来了一个移动生物实验室
Oh, I got a mobile bio-lab
这样好让她在床上恢复的时候补上工作
so she can catch up on her work while she recovers in bed.
别嫉妒  这是科学家的事
Don't be a jealous. It's a scientist thing.
来吧  雪宝宝  时我们
Come on, snow-poke. It's us.
非常冷
It's ice cold.
凯特琳
Caitlin.
救我
Help me.
什么时候凯特琳成了有冰霜的
Since when is Caitlin the frosty one?
她没有
She's not.
撑住 凯特琳
Hang on, Caitlin.
我们来处理
We're on the case.
我想我有了新的
I think I've come up with a new idea
让我们离开这里的办法
to get us out of this place.
住手
Stop!
你要干什么
What are you doing?
伊娃  想一下
Eva, think about it.
这是你唯一能控制的镜子
This is the only mirror that you can control.
所以这面镜子肯定有它与众不同的地方
So there's gotta be something different about it.
而且在我们弄明白它哪里不同之前
And until we can figure out what that is,
我们根本没有头绪
we're just working blind.
让开
Move.
所以为了检查它  你想把它杂碎
So to examine it, you want to smash it?
是啊  我们都知道
Yeah, I mean, we both know
你能让这面镜子复原
that you can put it back together,
所以我们为什么不把这个东西拆开
so let's just take this thing down,
一件一件分解
dissect it piece by piece,
看看里面的秘密究竟是什么
and learn what its secrets are.
行
Fine.
你想干什么就干什么
You do what you wanna do.
我要去我实验室了
Gonna go to my lab,
去研究真正能帮到我们的办法
and work on a plan that would actually help us.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
你能不能  或许快一点
Can you, uh, maybe hurry up?
爱瑞丝给我这把备用钥匙
You know, when Iris gave me a spare key,
是为了替她的植物浇水  不是去侵入她的电脑
it was to water her plants. It wasn't to hack her computer.
不能叫侵入爱瑞丝的电脑
It's not hacking Iris' computer
她不是真的爱瑞斯
if it's not really Iris.
话说回来你到底在找什么
What are you even looking for anyway?
这几周来任何
Anything that might be suspicious
可疑的东西
from the past few weeks.
-找到了  -你找到什么了
- Bingo. - What'd you find?
这张照片
This photo.
这是从卡米拉的相机里删掉的
It was deleted from Kamilla's camera,
但是在删除之前
but not before it was uploaded
被上传到《公民报》的云端服务器上了
to "The Citizen"'s cloud server.
你看到这段文字了吗
Do you see this text?
棱镜滤波器
Prismatic Filter.
那是什么
What is that?
这就是我们要用的科技手段
It's the science that we're gonna use
来测试这个假冒者真实的身份
to test our imposter's identity.
一举曝光她
Expose her for good.
这样就好多了  越来越有家的样子了
That's better. Much more homey.
换我来说是更接近
"Closer" Is how I'd describe it.
更接近母亲了
Closer to our Mother.
是时候进行下一步了
It's time for our next move.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
准备好了
Yes.
你呢
Are you?
准备好了
Yes.
伊娃的意愿是重要的
All that matters is Eva's will.
我们听从指令确保她必定成功
We follows orders and assure her success.
这就是我想要的
That's all I want.
我们需要专注
We need to focus.
还有一件物品母亲需要得到
There's still one item Mother needs to obtain
为了她能够解放
for her liberation.
而且是目前为止最危险的东西
And it's the most dangerous yet.
我看到你的短信了
Hey, I saw your text.
我以最快的速度赶过来了  有什么急事吗
I got here as fast as I could. What's the emergency?
那个急事很显然是你
You are. Apparently.
发生了什么
What's going on?
你不是爱瑞丝  就是这样
You're not Iris. That's what.
在你坦白你是谁或是什么东西之前
And you're not leaving here until you tell us
别想离开这里
who or what you are.
你们究竟在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
还有你的护手为什么在指着我
And why are you pointing that gauntlet at me?
这张照片由卡米拉的相机所拍摄
This photo was taken on Kamilla's camera.
你看到这个棱镜碎片了吗
You see the prismatic fragmentation?
只有你的图像被影响了
Only your image is affected.
我想相机的滤光器
I think that the camera's filter
展现了空间移位
is revealing a dimensional shift.
给我们展示了
Showing us things in the picture
相片里另一个维度的东西
from another dimension.
不属于我们这个维度的东西
Things that don't belong in ours.
塞西尔  你真的相信吗
Cecile, you actually believe this?
之前在你办公室你就不正常
You seemed off in your office earlier,
而且那张照片
and--and that photo.
那可能是任何东西
That could've been anything.
相机技术的小故障
A glitch in the camera tech.
各位  这太荒谬了
Guys, this is insane.
这个棱镜扫描仪是相机滤光器
This prismatic scanner is just a more powerful version
更强大的版本
of the camera's filter.
如果我错了  你真是来自这个维度
If I'm wrong, and you are from this dimension,
那么当棱镜波击中你的时候
then when the prismatic wave hits you,
你看起来会完全正常
you'll look completely normal.
但如果我是对的
But if I'm right,
你看起来就会像那张照片里的样子
you're gonna look just like that photo.
那请你得告诉我们真正的爱瑞丝在哪
And you're gonna tell us where the real Iris is.
巴里  你怎么能这么做
Barry, how could you do this?
拜托  我是你的妻子
For God's sake, I'm your wife.
好的
Okay.
你想看我到底是谁吗
You wanna see who I really am?
好吧
Fine.
我就给你看
I'll show you.
不不  我得知道
No, no--I have to know.
我得知道
I have to know.
肯定还有别人也听到这则喜讯
Someone else must have heard the good news too
因为他们给你送了份礼物  我给你送过去了
because they sent you a gift. I had it delivered.
你好  约瑟夫
Hello, Joseph.
这是你最后一次机会了  约瑟夫
This is your last chance. Joseph.
真实的人才能被威胁  伊娃
Threats are for real people, Eva.
而不是幽灵  因为你现在就是
Not phantoms. Because that's what you are.
因为你现在就是
Because that's what you are.
没人见过你
And no one saw you.
谢天谢地  你很安全
Thank God, you're safe.
我不安全  你也不安全
I'm not. Neither are you.
黑洞不是我们想的那样
Black Hole isn't what we think.
镜子
Mirror!
我知道
I know.
事实很伤人
The truth hurts.
巴里
Barry.
我只想你知道  如果发生什么  我
I just want you to know that if anything happens, I--
我都原谅你
I forgive you.
发生什么了
What's happening?
没什么
Nothing.
好了  够了
Okay--okay, that's-- that's enough.
不  出问题了  好吧
No, something's-- something's wrong, all right?
等一下
Just give it a minute.
我不知道她如何做到的
Look, I-- I don't know how she did this,
但你们得明白  这不是我妻子
but--but you have to see that this isn't my wife.
不  你不是我丈夫  巴里
No, you're not my husband, Barry.
你想知道真正的测试是什么吗
You wanna know what the real test is?
真正的巴里会更加努力
The real Barry would've fought harder.
他会努力回到家
He would've fought to come back home.
一整周过去了  你试都没尝试
A whole week went by and you never even tried.
你说过我是你的避雷针
You used to say that I was your lightning rod.
现在让我们看看你还是不是我的
Now let's see if you're still mine.
各位
Guys.
是我
I'm me.
我是真的巴里
I'm the real Barry.
-我是  -等等
- I'm-- hey! - Wait!
纳什  不要
Nash, no!
退后
Back up.
塞西尔
Cecile?
你相信我
You believe me?
我相信
Yes. I do.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
对不起  巴里
I'm sorry, Barry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
纳什  塞西尔
Nash! Cecile!
别听她的  那不是爱瑞丝
Don't listen to her. That's not Iris.
你可以选择停止游戏
You know, you can stop playing this game,
或者在那里等死  我不在乎
or rot in there. I don't care.
不管怎样  我都要找到我的丈夫
Either way, I'm gonna find my husband.
我应该注意到的
Ah, I should've noticed something.
我本应该发现的
I should've figured something out--
不  这不能怪你
No, no. No one's to blame.
他或是它装得太像了
He or it was pretty convincing.
如果他不是巴里  那他是什么
If that's not Barry, then what is he?
他好像是自己的镜像
He's like some mirror version of himself.
各位  约瑟夫·卡弗
Guys, Joseph Carver.
等等  你认为
Wait-- you think that
这和黑洞以及他们的反射芯片技术有关
this is related to Black Hole and their reflective chip technology?
没错
Yeah.
我不确定  这看起来
I don't know. That seems almost--
很有可能
No, that's possible.
我研究过麦克洛奇技术公司
I've seen that McCulloch tech up close and it--
他们的反射芯片技术
reflective chip technology, it's--
保守来说也是十分先进
it's far-reaching to say the least.
好的  这是我们目前最好的线索
Okay, well, um, then this might be our best lead.
你去看看能发现什么  纳什
Why don't you see what you can find, Nash?
我去找卡米拉
I will recoup with Kamilla,
做一些调查
and do some digging of our own.
你还好吗  塞西尔
Are you okay, Cecile?
没事
No, um...
只是有什么感觉不对劲
Something just doesn't feel right.
我理解
Yeah, no, I understand.
但是我们会调查清楚这一切
But we're gonna get to the bottom of this
把真的巴里带回来
and get the real Barry back.
我保证
I promise.
凯特琳的身体处于自身引发的"冰冻昏迷"
Caitlin's body essentially self-induced an "Ice coma"
迫使她进入冬眠状态
to force her to hibernate.
她就像是一块冷冻的电池
She's like a cold battery.
我们需要唤醒她
We just need to wake her up.
这需要你的帮助
That's where you come in.
我们没有电离导线
Since we don't have any ionized conductive wiring,
需要由你来做跨接电缆
you'll have to be the jumper cables.
明白
Got it.
好
Okay.
拉尔夫  你还好吗
Ralph! Are you all right?
她醒了吗
Is she good?
西斯科  她还好吗
Cisco, is she okay?
成功了吗
Did it work?
感谢艾莎
Oh, thank Elsa.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
谢谢
Thanks.
你刚才吓死我们了
You scared us for a minute there.
你能告诉我们发生什么事了吗
Can you tell us what happened?
我一个人在家
I was home alone,
光弹打出的伤口恶化了
and the wound from the light bullet was getting worse.
你与烈日的遭遇让伤势更重了
Sure your run-in with Sunshine didn't help.
对  所以我尝试用冰疗愈来治疗
Yeah, so I tried to ice heal it,
然后伤口裂开了
and that's when the wound ruptured.
这一定是我的免疫系统在保护我
It must have been my immune system's way of protecting me.
各位  我需要帮助
Guys, I need help.
你只要告诉我们你需要什么
You just tell us what you need.
我是说  我们知道有谁能帮助治愈
I mean, who do we know that can help with a...
光和冰冻造成的伤口呢
light-ice wound?
我们只能打给一个人
There's only one person we can call.
我妈妈
My mother.
她来了
Here she comes.
一切都按计划进行了吗
Everything went according to plan?
是的  是的  很顺利
Yeah. Yeah, we're fine.
一切都按计划进行
Everything went as planned.
你们俩去集合点
You guys go to the rendezvous.
我先去处理这件事  然后跟你们在那儿汇合
I'll handle this, and I'll meet you there.
我一直在监视巴里·艾伦
I've been watching Barry Allen.
他打算揭发你
He's planning on exposing you.
告诉我怎么办
Tell me what to do.
去见他
Go. Meet him.
其他的交给我
Leave the rest to me.
你不是爱瑞丝
You're not Iris.
在你坦白你是谁或是什么东西之前
And you're not leaving here until you tell us
就别想离开这里
who or what you are.
我们去执行任务吧
Now let's get what we came for.
做警察局长的好处之一就是
One of the benefits of being chief of police
我可以要求探监
is I can request prisoner interviews--
甚至可以让记者探监
even for press.
已锁定  不可进入
允许进入
好吧
Well...
这不是卡米拉·黄  辛格局长
if it isn't Kamilla Hwang, Chief Singh...
和爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦吗
and Iris West-Allen.
你们来这里有何贵干
To what do I owe the honor?
如果你帮我们  我们就能救你出去
If you help us, we can get you out of there.
我为什么要相信闪电侠的妻子
And why would I trust the wife of the Flash?
因为我不是爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦
Because I'm not Iris West-Allen.
我是她的镜像
I'm a reflection of her.
我们都是镜像
We're all reflections.
比与我们分享同一面孔的本体
Faster, stronger than our human counterparts
更快更强壮
whose faces we share.
我们唯一的愿望就是为母亲服务
And our only will is to serve our Mother.
真正的爱瑞丝绝对不会
The real Iris would never
主动释放我
offer to release me.
让我多了解一下你们的母亲
Tell me more about your Mother.
伊娃·麦克洛奇  她是位科...
Eva McCulloch. She was the sc--
我也是科学家  我知道伊娃·麦克洛奇是谁
I am a scientist. I know who Eva McCulloch is.
但她几年前就消失了
But she disappeared years ago.
她一直被困在另一个维度里
She's been trapped in another dimension.
一个镜像维度
A mirror one.
她需要你的某样东西
And she needs something from you.
你们需要我的血
You need my blood.
真伟大
How grand.
即使在这里  命运仍要让我扮演救世主的角色
Even in here, fate continues to cast me in the role of savior.
我们就要一滴
We just need one drop.
但是你现在就得决定
But you need to decide now.
我接受
I accept.
把我放出来你就能得到我的生命之血
Release me and you shall indeed have my life blood.
但是  这不是铁山监狱那粗劣的超能力者牢房
However, this is no crude metacell in Iron Heights.
你打算怎么破坏这
How do you propose to disrupt
有着三重备份协议的
a bio-degenerative containment matrix
生物负反馈控制矩阵
with triplicate backup protocols?
母亲有个理论
Mother has a theory.
我就是答案
I am the answer.
等等
Wait!
你会死
You'll die.
那这就是伊娃的意愿
Then it is Eva's will.
零号警报  监狱设备全体断电
Code zero! Facility-wide power failure!
所有层级  检查牢房
All levels. Check the cells.
我们有60秒直到守卫们...
We have 60 seconds until the guards--
你几乎就是个人
You're almost human.
也许还不仅如此
Maybe something more.
你服从你主人伊娃的意愿
You follow your master Eva's will,
但是我从你眼睛里看到了迟疑
but I see hesitation in your eyes.
你还有一点自己的意志
You have a modicum of will.
你是在计划骗我吗
Are you planning to trick me?
现在就告诉我
Tell me now!
你想要什么
What do you want?
只有伊娃的意愿
Only Eva's will.
谎言
Lies!
最后一次机会
Last chance.
你想要什么
What do you want?
活下来
To be alive.
你值得活下去
And you are worthy of it.
电力恢复
Power restored.
牢房封锁重新初始化
Cell containment reinitialized.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我们的计划  你不想逃跑吗
We had a plan. Don't you want to escape?
墙外有墙
There are walls beyond these walls.
我永远都不可能走出这里
I was never gonna just walk out of here.
但是对我来说自由有很多种方式
But there's more than one way for me to be free.
我们就叫它
Let's just call this
"放长线  钓大鱼"
"The long game."
现在  你走吧
Now go.
我会留在这  掩护我们的痕迹
I'll stay here and cover our tracks.
现在
Now!
跑  爱瑞丝
Run, Iris.
跑
Run!
牢房控制
塞西尔
Cecile?
我没有所有的真相
I don't have all the facts.
但是凭我有的告诉我
And the ones I do have tell me
你不是你口中那个人
that you're not who you say you are.
你是巴里
You are Barry.
我心里清楚
I know it in my heart.
我愿意用我的命去赌
And I'm willing to bet my life on it.
现在把爱瑞丝救回来
Now go get Iris back.
做得好
Good work.
你将把拉姆齐的血滴到你镜子的那面
You'll apply Ramsey's blood on your side of the mirror.
一旦它完全吸收了
Once it is fully absorbed,
我会启动我这边的反射芯片扩张调制器
I will activate the R-CEM on my side.
一起  它们将重新设定
Together, they will reconfigure
燃烧生物体的空间壁垒
the molecular stability of the dimensional barrier
分子稳定性
that burns organic matter.
在两个世界之间建造一条安全的通道
Creating a safe passageway between the two worlds.
下一次我跟你说话的时候
Next time I speak to you,
我就可以站在你身边了
I will be standing right next to you.
不受拘束
Liberated.
保证成功
Success is assured.
我看那可未必
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
我妻子在哪
Where's my wife?
我再问一遍
I'll ask you one more time.
我妻子在哪
Where is my wife?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我什么都看到了
I saw everything.
你从一开始就把我作为目标
You targeted me from the very beginning.
我的痛苦你只品尝到了一点
You suffered a fraction of my pain.
但要不了多久
But in just a few,
我就自由了
I will be liberated.
巴里一定会阻止你的
Barry is gonna stop you.
我们俩会阻止你的
We both will.
我曾以为我的爱人也会给予我力量
I used to think my love gives me strength too.
但镜子向我展示了真相
The mirror showed me the truth.
我也来让你看清真相
Let me do the same for you.
她说你总是会妨碍到她
She says you're always gonna be in her way.
但现在你太慢了  已经没法阻止我了
And now you're too slow to stop me.
妨碍到谁
Whose way?
是谁让你做这些的
Who's making you do this?
你真应该当心你身边的东西
You should really mind your surroundings.
我妻子在哪
Where is my wife?
你想到的只有她吗
She's all you can think about, huh?
你觉得我怎么样  巴里
What do you think about me, Barry?
这些日子以来...
All those days...
这么多周
Weeks.
在你身边的都不是她  是我
It wasn't her. It was me.
我们一起吃饭
Enjoying meals together.
一起聊每天发生的事
Talking about our day.
一起睡觉
Sharing your bed.
闭嘴
Oh, shut up.
我要杀了你
I am going to kill you.
想得美
Unlikely.
这个计划我已经筹谋五年了
I have been working on this plan for half a decade.
这是我的创作
This is my creation.
她就是我  我就是她
She is me, and I am her.
她能感觉到的  我也能
What she feels, I feel.
我们绝不能失败
And we cannot lose.
他们能体会到你对卡夫的感觉吗
Do they feel what you feel for Carver?
什么
What?
他们还爱他吗
Do they still love him?
我不爱我的丈夫
I don't love my husband.
我想要他的命
I want to end him.
那你为什么还称他为你的丈夫
Then why do you still call him your husband?
你跟从前一样  一样的盲目
You are just as blinded as you were before.
他还会用同样的伎俩玩弄你
And he is going to trick you in the exact same way.
不要再说了
Stop talking.
因为你仍然爱着他
Because you still love him.
不  我没有
No! I don't!
你睿智的大脑就是想不明白
Your brilliant mind couldn't figure out
他没有在乎过你
that he didn't care about you.
闭嘴
Shut up!
你在这等了多久  伊娃
How long did you sit here, Eva,
一直渴望被拯救
pining for rescue
直到你意识到你早就被遗弃了
before you realized that you had been abandoned?
我恨他
I hate him!
我要让他受尽折磨
I want him to suffer! Suffer, suffer!
折磨  折磨
Suffer! Suffer!
折磨
Suffer!
爱瑞丝
Iris?
无尽的痛苦和折磨
Suffer and suffer and suffer!
折磨
Suffer! Suffer!
爱瑞丝  爱瑞丝
Iris. Iris.
我不会和你打
I won't fight you.
我不会和你打了
I won't fight you anymore.
你的原型是爱瑞丝
You were made from Iris.
你有着她的一部分内心
A part of her heart is inside you.
我见到过你的善良
I've seen you be kind.
我见到过你的欢笑
I've seen you laugh.
我知道那并不全是谎言
I know that wasn't all a lie.
你可以成为更好的人
You can be more than this.
不是爱瑞丝
Not Iris, but...
而是你自己
yourself.
你必须自己想要改变
You have to want it.
不
No.
你要自己做出选择
You have to choose it.
我选择我自己
I--I choose me.
去找爱瑞丝
Go find Iris.
去找她  巴里
Go find her, Barry.
去救爱瑞丝
Go save Iris.
快去
Go.
巴里
Barry.
我有生命了
I feel alive.
看你逼我做了些什么
Look what you made me do.
不  对不起
No, I'm sorry!
本来不必这样的  闪电侠
This didn't have to be like this, Flash.
你不知道在那里面的感受
You don't know what it's like in there.
我必须出来
I had to get out.
爱瑞丝
Iris...
她在哪里
Where--where is she?
她还在我离开的世界中
She's still in the world I left behind.
还有其他我留下的保险措施
Along with the rest of my insurance policy.
辛格局长和你的朋友卡米拉
Chief Singh, and your friend, Kamilla.
他们很安全
They're safe.
安全的时间则取决于你
How long is up to you.
现在呢
So...what?
你要杀了我
Now you're gonna kill me?
没有必要
There's no need for that.
你身受重伤
You're wounded.
还失去了速度
You lost your speed.
你的自愈速度不如以往
And your healing is not what is used to be.
你根本成不了威胁  对吧
You're not much of a threat, are you?
你别来妨碍我  闪电侠
You just stay out of my way, Flash.
我也不会妨碍你
And I'll stay out of yours.
我还有未竟之业
I have unfinished business to attend to.
我还要解放整个世界
And a whole world to liberate.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
哦，谢谢..
Oh, thank...
爱丽丝，我..
Iris, I...
我不知道以为你能听到我说话是不是疯了
I don't know if it's crazy to think that you can hear me.
♪ 说，“这太疯狂了”，你总是这样做♪
♪ Say, "It's mad," you always do ♪
我想现在我只需要相信它
I guess right now I just need to believe it.
♪ 告诉我这怎么不是真的♪
♪ Tell me how it's not true ♪
♪ 这些翅膀可以托起我们两个♪
♪ These wings could lift us both ♪
我想念你
I miss you.
♪ 但你不这么认为
♪ But you don't think so
太多了
So much.
♪ 你是我想要的一切，所以
♪ You are all I wanted, so
♪ 如果我把它都扔掉了
♪ If I threw it all away
♪ 我还会有你吗？
♪ Would I still have you?
如果我想踩刹车的话♪
♪ If I tried to hit the brakes ♪
♪ 你能看穿吗？♪
♪ Would you see right through? ♪
♪ 这不是酒后甜蜜的爱情♪
♪ This ain't the fair-weather love ♪
♪ 就像我习惯的那样，没有♪
♪ Like I'm used to, no ♪
♪ 如果我把它都扔掉了
♪ If I threw it all away
我知道你可能听不见我说话，巴里，但是.
I know you probably can't hear me, Barry, but...
♪ 我还会有你吗？
♪ Would I still have you?
离开你一天比一天更让人心痛
Being away from you hurts more and more every day.
但我仍然抱有希望，因为我知道
But I still have hope because I know
你在外面战斗
that you are out there fighting
把我带回家
to get me back home.
♪ 按住我
♪ Hold me down
如果你能听到我说话..
If you can hear me...
♪ 说我们永远不会死
♪ Say we'll never die
我想我只是想让你知道.
I guess I just need you to know that...
♪ 但你不这么认为
♪ But you don't think so
我爱你
I love you.
♪ 这就是我想要的全部
♪ This is all I wanted
而那份爱是恒久不变的
And that love is constant.
跨越多个维度
Across dimensions.
♪ 如果我把它都扔掉了
♪ If I threw it all away
跨越时间
Across time.
如果我试图击中♪
♪ If I try to hit the breaks ♪
穿过世界末日然后回来
Through the end of the world and back.
♪ 你能看穿吗？♪
♪ Would you see right through? ♪
♪ 这不是集市..
♪ This ain't the fair...
如果我了解你的话..
And if I know you...
♪ 就像我习惯的那样
♪ Like I'm used to
我知道你不只是为了找到回家的路而奋斗
I know you aren't just fighting to find your way home.
♪ 如果我把它都扔掉了
♪ If I threw it all away
我会找到卡米拉的
And I'm gonna find Kamilla.
我会找到辛格的
And I'm gonna find Singh.
但最重要的是..
But most of all...
我会把你救回来的
I'm gonna get you back.
我会想办法回到你身边的
I'm gonna find my way back to you.
♪ 我还会有你吗？
♪ Would I still have you?
格雷格，动动你的头
Greg, move your head.